# **IDRIS YUSUF**

### **Frontend Developer**



https://www.linkedin.com/in/idrisyusuf-663117a6/



https://github.com/drizzy009/



idris.dev0x@gmail.com

+234 810 106 4478

## **PROFILE**

I am a conscientious frontend developer with a proven two-year track record in website development, emphasizing HTML, CSS, and an ongoing commitment to enhancing my JavaScript and React skills. Notable for my meticulous research approach, I currently contribute to the development and maintenance of websites at Axon Analytics Limited. Collaborating effectively with the UI and Graphic design team, I focus on optimizing layouts and improving user flows. Enthusiastic about opportunities to apply my research skills and contribute to the success of innovative teams.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

0

**Frontend Developer Intern** 

**Axon Analytics Limited** 

07/2021 - 08/2022

**Frontend Developer** 

**Axon Analytics Limited** 

08/2022 - Present

Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.

Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow. Work with senior developer to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients.

Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.

#### 0

#### **Achievements:**

- Built over 40 Landing pages for clients on requests within and before given timeline.
- Built an event landing page using reactjs that automatically generates QR codes for attendees upon sign-up. Integrated the QR codes into a custom HTML email template, sending personalized emails with embedded QR codes to registered users.
- Learned to integrate an AI Powered Growth Marketing suite that enables brands to listen, analyze, and converse & improve conversions across Mobile App and Website.
- Built a fully functional website from scratch for a client using a UI/UX provided by the product designers.
- Managed multiple client WordPress sites, including setting up new sites, maintaining and updating existing sites, and troubleshooting any issues that arose.
- Successfully maintained the functionality of multiple plugins across client sites, including identifying and resolving conflicts and errors.

# Technologies used:

Wordpress

ReactJS

HTML/CSS

jQuery

Tailwindcss

# **SKILLS & TOOLS**

HTML/CSS

React

Javascript

**Tailwind CSS** 

Wordpress

**Others** 

Wordpress

Figma

SASS

# **EDUCATION**

BSc in Aquaculture & Fisheries Mgt

Federal University of Agriculture, Abeokuta

2014 - 2021

### **NATIONALITY**

Nigerian

SASS